mycleanpc.com 2017-03-14

# Personal Identifying Information (PII) - Privacy Policy | MyCleanPC.com

This Privacy Policy was last updated and effective as of October 17, 2016. 

You linked to this Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") via our technical support website that is owned by USTech Support Corporation ("USTechSupport", "us", "our" or "we"). This Privacy Policy governs your use of www.mycleanpc.com (including, without limitation, both mobile and online versions of our website), and also applies to your use of all features, software, applications, databases, content, downloads and other services that we make available through the website (collectively, referred to herein as the "Website"), regardless of how you access or use the Website, whether via personal computers, mobile devices or otherwise. This Privacy Policy does not apply to our data collection activities offline or otherwise outside of our Website. 

It is important for you to understand what information we collect about you during your visit to our Website and what we do with that information. Please note that your visit to our Website is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service. By using our Website, you consent and agree to our Privacy Policy and Terms of Service and our collection, use and sharing of your information and data, and other activities, as described below. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not provide us with any personal information and do not use our Website. To the extent we provide you notice on our Website of different or additional privacy policies or practices ( _e.g._ , at the point of our collection), those additional terms shall govern such data collection and use. 

### Linkable Table of Contents

  1. Information Collection
  2. Use/Disclosure of Personal Information
  3. Information Security
  4. Access and Choice
  5. Technology Utilized / Tracking Technologies
  6. Do Not Track Signals
  7. Ads and Information About You
  8. External Links
  9. Social Media Widgets
  10. Blogs/Forums
  11. International Users
  12. Your California Privacy Rights
  13. Notification of Changes
  14. Contact Information

## 1\. Information Collection

We collect personally identifiable information about you via our Website when you provide it through various forms and places on the Website, such as when you provide it in order to open an account with us or purchase software licenses and technical support services from us. You may browse our Website without providing any personal information; however if, for example, you decide to purchase technical support, we will ask you for your name, age, the password to your computer in the event you purchase certain technical support services, billing address, phone number(s), email address, and payment information such as credit/debit card number, expiration dates, PayPal or third party payment information. Also, to the extent we offer identity protection services (if ever) and you purchase them, USTechSupport may need to collect your social security number. If you choose to complete a user registration form, survey, we may ask you for personal information, such as your contact information ( _e.g._ , name, e-mail address and mailing address). Occasionally, we may also ask you for other demographic information, such as gender, income level, and information about your prior experiences with the USTechSupport's products. If we combine demographic information with the personal information we collect directly from you on our Website, we will treat the combined data as personal information under this Privacy Policy. When you submit your personally identifiable or demographic information on one of the Website, you are giving your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

We may receive information about you from your friends and others that use the Website, such as when they submit your information to us about you. Additionally, we may, from time to time, supplement the information we collect directly from you on our Website with outside records from third parties for various purposes, including to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our content to you and to offer you opportunities that may be of interest to you. You may delete the other person's information from your account or the other person may contact us at [support2@ustechsupport.com](mailto:support2@ustechsupport.com) to request that we remove their information from our database. Note: Although you can remove the information from your account for future orders, the other person's information may be retained with the original transaction for auditing and legal purposes. In no other circumstances do our statements under this Privacy Policy apply to information we receive about you from third parties. 

We also use the tracking technologies described in Section 5 below in order to automatically (or passively) collect, store or accumulate certain non-personally identifiable information concerning your use of this Website, such as information regarding which of our pages are most popular and remembering you and your preferences, your IP address, UDID or other unique identifier, device functionality (including browser, operator system, hardware, mobile network information), device location, device characteristics, city, time zone, MAC address, referring and exit URL and similar information. Information gathered may be used in aggregate form for internal and other business purposes, such as generating statistics, developing marketing plans, customizing content, tailoring our products, services and advertising to suit the personal interests of you and others and improving the Website. This usage information may be stored or accessed using a variety of technologies that may be downloaded to your personal computer, browser, laptop, tablet, mobile phone or other device whenever you visit or interact with our Website. We may share or transfer such aggregate, non-personally identifiable information with or to our affiliates, licensees, partners and other third parties. We may combine automatically collected Website usage information with your personal information. In those cases, we will apply this Privacy Policy to the combined information. 

When we provide technical support services to you, we also may collect (in some instances with your authorization first), the following information about your computer or other device: 

  * Technical information about the basic configuration and operation of your computer, including operating system version, processor type, disk space, memory space, and number of drivers;
  * Information about USTechSupport software on your computer, including the version and when it was installed and upgraded; and
  * Certain events that occur on your computer, including when USTechSupport software is installed, when USTechSupport software receives threat updates, and when errors occur in USTechSupport software.

This information collected as part of our provision of technical support services to you is sent only to USTechSupport when you reach out to us for assistance, and it is stored in an anonymous form that cannot be used to identify you. By way of explanation, although USTechSupport knows, based on the information, that there is a customer with a certain kind of computer that is performing certain functions, USTechSupport, does not know the customer's identity unless you tell it to us. In the event that it is necessary for USTechSupport to learn your identity in order to diagnose certain kinds of problems or to monitor your computer for certain events, you will be asked to authorize USTechSupport to collect the additional information. You can make your selection as to whether USTechSupport may collect this additional information before the software is installed or buy using a control panel included in the software. You can change your selection concerning this feature by using the control panel. 

For a complete list of the information we may collect as part of the services we offer, click here. 

The Website is intended for a general audience. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. We will delete any personal information collected that we later determine to be from a user younger than the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13 and believe he or she has disclosed personal information to us, please contact Customer Service using the contact information in Section 14 below. 

## 2\. Use/Disclosure of Personal Information

The USTechSupport and its affiliates and subsidiaries may use your information as follows: 

  * to place an order made through the Website and fulfill your order request, including to send you a software activation code;
  * to improve our technical support and the overall experience at the Website;
  * to process transactions or provide you with information such as to send you electronic newsletters or to provide you with special offers or promotional and marketing materials on behalf of us or third parties, including to let you know about new products, services or upcoming events;
  * to improve the Website, marketing endeavors and our Website offerings;
  * to customize your experience on the Website or to serve you specific content or ads that are relevant to you;
  * to provide customer support;
  * to contact you with regard to your use of the Website and, in our discretion, changes to the Website and/or Website's policies;
  * to identify your service, support and Website preferences so that you can be informed of new or additional products, services and promotions;
  * to enable you to participate in a variety of the Website's features such as to enable you to participate in online entry sweepstakes, contests or other promotions;
  * to improve the overall experience at the Website;
  * for internal business purposes; and
  * for purposes disclosed at the time you provide your information or as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy.

If for any reason you would no longer like to receive email marketing messages from the USTechSupport, you may follow the instructions contained within our promotional emails or please click here. Please allow up to ten (10) days for us to process your request. This will not affect subsequent subscriptions and if your opt-out is limited to certain types or categories of emails the opt-out will be so limited. Please note, if you opt not to receive marketing emails from the USTechSupport, you may still receive "transactional" email messages regarding your account, use of the Website or your order ( _e.g._ , order confirmation, shipping information, recall notices, customer service notifications, etc.). If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact Customer Service. 

The USTechSupport may share non-personal information, such as aggregated user statistics, with third parties. The USTechSupport may also share and sell your information, such as your name, email address, mailing address and/or telephone number to business partners, vendors and other third party organizations to provide you with information about products, services and special offers we think may interest you or to improve our products, services and advertising. If you are a California resident, you have the right to request additional information about this sharing, so please see Section 12 below. In addition, we may share the information we have collected about you, including personal information, as disclosed at the time you provide your information and as described below or otherwise in this Privacy Policy. 

We may contract with companies or individuals to provide certain services including email and hosting services, credit card processing, shipping, data management, surveys and marketing, promotional services, to assist in preventing or deterring fraud, etc. We call them our "Service Providers". We may share personally identifiable information with Service Providers solely as appropriate for them to perform their functions, but they may not use such information for any other purpose. 

We do not share your credit card information with unaffiliated third parties unless you authorize us to do so, or if it is necessary to fulfill our responsibilities, including, but not limited to, delivering a product or service that you order. 

Some of our pages utilize framing techniques to serve content to/from our partners while preserving the look and feel of our Website. Please be aware that you are providing your personal information to these third parties and not to USTechSupport. 

The USTechSupport may, in its sole discretion, disclose personal information in special cases: (1) when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the rights of the USTechSupport or to anyone that could be harmed by such activities; (2) when we believe in good faith that the law requires it; (3) to a subsequent owner, co-owner or operator of a Website or applicable database or in connection with a merger, consolidation, restructuring, the sale of substantially all of our interests and/or assets or other corporate change, including, during the course of any due diligence process; and (4) in situations involving threats to the physical safety of any person. 

## 3\. Information Security

We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), an advanced security protocol that protects your credit card information and ensures secure online ordering. SSL Internet connections are encrypted, and thus protect all credit card ordering information, including your name, address and credit card number, so it cannot be read in transit. We use secure technology, privacy protection controls, and restrictions on employee access, to safeguard your personal information. Please note, however, that although we employ industry-standard security measures to safeguard the security of your personal information, no transmissions made on or through the Internet are guaranteed to be secure. Please note that we cannot ensure the security of any information you transmit to us, and you use our Website and provide us with your information at your own risk. 

## 4\. Access and Choice

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove, or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at [support2@ustechsupport.com](mailto:support2@ustechsupport.com) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe. 

## 5\. Technology Utilized / Tracking Technologies

Because of the manner in which we offer our services, we cannot provide services to customers who do not permit our use of cookies or whose browsers are set to reject cookies. 

We and our marketing partners, affiliates, or analytics or service providers, use technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags, browser and device fingerprinting, network traffic monitoring, active scripting, recognition technologies and scripts, to analyze trends, administer the Website, tracking users' movements around the Website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual and aggregated basis. 

There may be other tracking technologies now and later devised and used by us in connection with the Website. Further, third parties may use tracking technologies in connection with our Website, which may include the collection and storing of information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or online services. 

We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as a DoubleClick cookie) together to report how your ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our Website. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads based on your visit to our Website and/or other sites and online services. To learn more about how to opt out of Google's use of first-party cookies, click [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). To learn more about how to opt out of DoubleClick's use of cookies, visit the DoubleClick opt-out page, [here](https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/2839090?hl=en). 

Additionally, the Website may use Adobe's analytics and on-site personalization services. See <http://www.adobe.com/privacy/analytics.html> for more information. To learn about opting out of the use of Adobe cookies for analytics and on-site personalization, visit <http://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html#4>. After you opt out of the use of Adobe cookies for analytics and on-site personalization, Adobe will no longer collect and analyze information via cookies associated with your browser for these services. When you opt out, Adobe will place opt-out cookies on your browser. If you delete your cookies, change browsers, or change devices, you will need to repeat this opt-out process. Also, please note that this opt-out process will work only if your browser is set to accept all cookies. We may not control those tracking technologies and we are not responsible for them. However, you consent to potentially encountering third-party tracking technologies in connection with use of our Website and accept that our statements under this Privacy Policy do not apply to the Tracking Technologies or practices of such third parties. 

The Website may use code provided by Yahoo! to collect information about goods and services of interest, including, in connection with the collection of information to provided behaviorally targeted or interest-based advertisements to you as further explained in Section 7 below. To learn more about the choices offered by Yahoo!, visit the Yahoo! Ad Interest manager at <https://aim.yahoo.com/aim/us/en/optout/>. 

We use Local Storage, such as HTML5, to store content information and preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our Website or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity also use Flash cookies and HTML5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5. To manage Flash cookies, please click here: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>. 

## 6\. Do Not Track Signals

Some web browsers are developing or offering signals or other mechanisms for the expression of consumer choice regarding the collection of information about an individual consumer's online activities over time and across third-party web sites or online services ( _e.g._ , a "Do Not Track" ("DNT") signal). A DNT signal is a HTTP header field indicating your preference regarding tracking or cross-site user tracking. We do not monitor or take any action with respect to DNT signals. 

## 7\. Ads and Information About You

We may work with third parties, such as network advertisers and ad exchanges that use tracking technologies on our Website in order to provide tailored advertisements on our behalf and/or on behalf of other advertisers across the Internet and we may use third party analytics service providers to evaluate and provide us and/or third parties with information about the use of these ads on third party sites and viewing of ads and of our content. Network advertisers are third parties that display advertisements, which may be based on your activities (including past visits to our Website) across the Internet and mobile media ("Behavioral Ads"). Behavioral Ads enable us to target advertisements to you for products and services in which we believe you might be interested. If you object to receiving Behavioral Ads from us on third party sites, you can learn more about your ability to limit Behavioral Ads below. Our third party ad network and exchange providers, the advertisers and/or traffic measurement services may themselves set and access their own technologies on your device and track certain behavioral usage information via a device identifier. These third party technologies may be set to, among other things: (a) help deliver advertisements to you that you might be interested in; (b) prevent you from seeing the same advertisements; and (c) understand the usefulness of the advertisements that have been delivered to you. 

Statements regarding our practices do not apply to the methods for collecting information used by these third parties or the use of the information that such third parties collect. We do however work with third parties to make efforts to have you provided with information on their practices and any available opportunity to exercise choice. We make no representations regarding the policies or practices of third party advertisers or advertising networks or exchanges or related third parties. 

Further, while sites use a variety of companies to serve advertisements, you may wish to visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp>, which provides information regarding this practice by Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI") members, and your choices regarding having this information used by these companies, including the "opt-out" procedures of NAI members. Opting out of one or more NAI members only means that those NAI members no longer will be allowed under their own rules to deliver Behavioral Ads to you, but does not mean you will no longer receive any targeted content and/or ads. Also, if your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you visit this opt-out page, or you subsequently erase your cookies, use a different device or change web browsers, your NAI opt-out may not, or may no longer, be effective. You may also opt-out of receiving Behavioral Ads on participating sites and services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance ("DAA") website at <http://www.aboutads.info/choices> (or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). Similar limitations may apply to the DAA opt-out. We are not responsible for effectiveness of or compliance with any third parties' opt-out options or programs. 

## 8\. External Links

Our Website may offer links to and from other third party sites. Other sites have their own policies regarding privacy. If you visit one of these sites, you may want to review the privacy policy on that site. For example, you may have linked to the USTechSupport's site through a banner advertisement on another site. In such cases the site you have linked from may collect information from people who click on the banner or link. You may want to refer to the privacy policies on those sites to see how they collect and use this information. 

## 9\. Social Media Widgets

Our Website may include social media features ("Features"), such as the Facebook Like button, and widgets, such as the Share This button or interactive applications or mini-programs that run on our Website. These Features may collect your Internet protocol address, which page you are visiting on our Website, and may set a cookie to enable the Features to function properly. The use of this functionality may involve the third-party operator providing certain information, including Personal Information, to us. If you click on social media icons on the Website (such as for Facebook, Twitter or Instagram), those actions may be associated with, and we may have access to, your Personal Information you provided on those third-party sites or applications. If so, we will then treat it as Personal Information under this Privacy Policy, since we are collecting it as a result of your accessing of and interaction on our Website. Features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Website. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy statement of the USTechSupport providing it. You should review the applicable third-party privacy policies before using such third-party tools on our Website. 

## 10\. Blogs/Forums

Our Website may, from time to time, offer publicly accessible blogs or community forums where you can submit ideas, photographs, writings, music, video, audio recordings, computer graphics, pictures, data, information about your location, questions, comments, suggestions or other content, including personal information. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. Please note that USTechSupport does not control who will have access to the information that you choose to make public, and cannot ensure that parties who have access to such publicly available information will respect your privacy or keep it secure. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [support2@ustechsupport.com](mailto:support2@ustechsupport.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. We are not responsible for the privacy or security of any information that you make publicly available on the Website or what others do with information you share with them on the Website. We are not responsible for the accuracy, use or misuse of any user content that you disclose or receive from third parties through the Website. 

## 11\. International Users

Our Website is operated in the United States and intended for users located in the United States. Like almost every website, our Website can be accessed by an international audience. If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that information we collect, including personal information, will be transferred to, and processed, stored and used in the United States. The data protection laws in the United States may differ from those of the country in which you are located, and your personal information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in the United States according to laws of the United States. In addition, such data may be stored on servers located outside your resident jurisdiction and in jurisdictions which may have less stringent privacy practices than your own. By using the Website or providing us with any information, you consent to the transfer to, and processing, usage, sharing and storage of your information, including personal information, in the United States as set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

## 12\. Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of USTechSupport who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding twelve (12) calendar months. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to: 

USTechSupport LLC General Counsel 100 N. Sepulveda Boulevard Suite 1600 El Segundo, California 90245 Attn: California Privacy Rights 

## 13\. Notification of Changes

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post the revised policy here. If we make any material changes, we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Website prior to the change becoming effective. As we may make changes at any time without notifying you, we suggest that you periodically consult this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website after the changes are posted constitutes your agreement to the changes, both with regard to information we have previously collected from you and with regard to information we collect from you in the future. If you do not agree to the changes, please discontinue your use of our Website. 

## 14\. Contact Information

You can access, update or correct your information, or otherwise ask us questions about this Privacy Policy by contacting USTechSupport as follows: 

Customer Escalation Team USTechSupport LLC 100 N. Sepulveda Boulevard Suite 1600 El Segundo, California 90245 Email: [support2@ustechsupport.com](mailto:support2@ustechsupport.com)
